infocoverage.com 2017-09-20

# Privacy Policy

## **Privacy Policy for www.infocoverage.com**

These Privacy Policies/Terms of Service (mentioned below) are made between www.infocoverage.com and you as a website user.

We respect the privacy of our visitors utmost. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.infocoverage.com and how it is used. By using InfoCoverage.com you agree to be legally bound by these terms.

**Web Browser Cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance best user experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their computer/mobile memory to track information about them. Users have full rights to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.infocoverage.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.infocoverage.com and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense.

**Under Age Privacy Protection Act**

Protecting the privacy of the child is especially important to us. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at www.infocoverage.com from those we actually know are under 14, and no part of this website is designed for a child under 14.

**Third Party Website Links**

InfoCoverage.com website may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or maintained by us. InfoCovergae has no control over it, and so we don’t have any specific idea about content practices of any third party websites. In addition, InfoCoverage.com cannot edit the content of any third party website. But we encourage you to be aware when you move out of the InfoCoverage.com and must read the terms and conditions to other websites that you visit.

**Changes To Privacy Policy/Terms of Uses**

We reserved the rights to make changes in our privacy policy when needed. But for user conveince about new terms, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site about privacy policy changes. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of any changes.

**Your Acceptance for Terms of Service**

By using InfoCopverage.com you accept our policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be consider your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any query or want any more information about our privacy policy then feel free to contact us directly via email at contact@infocoverage.com or author’s email tapeshwar3@gmail.com.
